http://www.shelter-kit.com/privacy-policy.html

Contact
Shelter-Kit Privacy Policy:
We respect your privacy. We do not share your personal information with any other party for marketing or contact purposes.What Information Do We Collect?When you visit our site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you actively choose to disclose (Active Information); and usage information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate anonymous basis as you and others browse our site (Passive Information).Active Information You Choose to ProvideIn order to receive updates via email, we require you to disclose the following information:·         Your email addressIf you supply us with your postal address on-line, you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.Other Active Information would include any other information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.Passive Information CollectedFor each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes and collects only the consumer’s domain name and/or IP address, (where possible), but not the e-mail address. Passive information, such as what pages consumers access or visit, is also collected.How Do We Use the Information Collected?Broadly speaking, persons we employ directly, or as contractors or agents at our direction, use Active Information for purposes of administering our business activities and providing customer services such as support. We use Passive Information to gather information about our users and to enhance and design our site to make it easier, faster, and friendlier to use. We do not connect any Passive information to your personal information or email address. The Passive information we collect is used for internal review to improve the content of our Web page and is then discarded. Active information is used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site. It is not shared with other organizations unless authorized by this organization for the benefit of our members and site users. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, please send us an email at the address shown at the bottom of each page at this site or contact us in writing at the postal address shown there.Your Information In Relation to Others We Link ToYou are able to access other websites through this site. When you do so you are doing so subject to their policies regarding privacy and data collection and you should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. When you choose to shop at such sites, you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before making purchases.Sharing Information with Third PartiesWe may disclose anonymous information about user habits, characteristics, and user patterns, based on aggregate user statistics on our site to legitimate third parties. However, at this time there are no third parties involved.Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by LawWe may be required by law or government agency to disclose the Active Information you have provided to us.How Do We Secure Active Information and Passive Information?We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction, of Active Information and Passive Information. Communications you may have with us via email or U.S. Mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means.We reserve the right to revise this policy at our discretion. Please check back on this site as this policy may be revised from time to time without notice to you.
Home
About Us
Our Kit Designs
Popular House Plans
Garage/Apartments Plans
House, Barn & Garage Plans
Pricing
How to Order
